4F., No. 111-15, Fuxing Rd., Luzhou Dist., New Taipei City 24744, Taiwan (R.O.C.)

About

I'm a computer engineer with more than ten years of professional experience. I'm specialized in all kinds of internet technology, including front-end and back-end. My major work is on web server build-up and maintain, planning project, schedule control. I incline to be a superior developer.

Experience

COMMSCOPE ARRIS RUCKUS, STAFF SOFTWARE ENGINEER - 2019/10 - NOW

- Maintain system operation to ensure that P1 bugs can be diagnosed within 24 hours and eliminated within 72 hours (ext.js)
- Use JIRA to execute Scrum projects and develop new features on schedule
 - Use Angular and RxJS

ZOEK INC., SENIOR ENGINEER - 2017/05 - 2019/10

<u>FunNow</u> is a service platform for real-time booking all kinds of entertainment, include massage/spa, fine dining & drinking, late check-in, lashes and manicure, Fun outdoor activities.

- Build a website from scratch using the PHP slim framework, and create transaction page with Vue.js 2.x to improved user experience
- Use website analysis tools to improve the transaction process page, effectively reducing the bounce rate by 13% (GA, FB pixel, hotjar)
- Integrate LINE Pay and Apple Pay in the checkout process to increase the transaction success rate by 6%
- Design and implement Restful API in Golang
- Established product sales time by using ElasticSearch and schedule calculations through AWS Lambda
- Use FCM (firebase cloud message) to establish a web push notification mechanism

SAGACITY TECHNOLOGY CO., LTD., SOFTWARE ENGINEER – 2013/04 - 2014/07, 2015/07 - 2017/02 QuizFun 考尚樂 which is a simulation test and learning platform with knowledge sharing as the core.

Management team with Scrum, built a development and test environment platform on AWS. participated in background function development, front-end automation process (Gulp), studied different technologies and import into our product:

- Design and develop the question editing interface with React.js
- Design and develop the PDF / Word file upload question transpose tool with Vue.js 1.x and Vuex, and boosted the efficiency of data establishment around 80%

EATME CATERING CONSULTING CO.,LTD., PRODUCT MANAGER - 2014/07 - 2015/06

- United designer and engineers as a small team to brainstorm EatMe App and running project with scrum
- Create Eatme official website with Laravel 4.2 and build a blog system including front-end display and back-end management
 - Integrate third-party payment API to sell EatMe Cards
- Create a landing page to display product features

COMPAL ELECTRONICS, INC., DESIGN LEADER - 2011/08 - 2013/04

Porting audio function on android. Design IPC (Inter-Process Communication) mechanism for transformer pad project and demo at Computex 2012.

ACADEMIA SINICA, SOFTWARE ENGINEER – 2007/01 - 2011/07

Digital archive system and Unencoded Chinese Character technology application development.

- Text source evolution (文字源演變), electronic stamp (電子圖章), e-card (電子賀卡) technology license to IQChinese Corp.
- Chinese character query (漢字查詢), e-card (電子賀卡) technology authorized to the WingNet Technology Co., Ltd.

Education

National Chung Cheng University - Master of Computer Science and Information Engineering, SEPTEMBER 2004 - JUNE 2006

Skills

- Proficient: Git, JavaScript, Sass, Gulp, Webpack, Vue.js, Angular
- Intermediate: LAMP, Golang, ElasticSearch, Node.js, React.js, AWS, Slim Framework, Laravel

Reference

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/soarlin/

Github : https://github.com/soarlin Blog : https://soarlin.github.io/